Shashika Kahatapitiya

E-mail: kahatapitiyagsj@gmail.com Website: https://www.linkedin.com/in/shashika-

kahatapitiya-17a590209/

Phone: +94 77 528 1377 Address: 1st lane,

Weliwita, Malabe.

Job Role

Junior / Associate Software Engineer / Developer

Profile Info

Hard-working Information Technology major currently attending Sri Lanka Institute of Information Technology, with
more than one year of work experience. Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of web design, database
development, and application development skills to successfully fill the Software Engineer role at your company.
Frequently praised as efficient by my peers, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Sri Lanka Institute of Information Technology

• Bsc.Hons Special Degree In Information Technology

Diploma in English and Literature

Aquinas University Colledge

• Intermediate Level

Advanced Level Examination - Biological Science

Mihindu Central Colledge

- Biology C
- · Chemistry C
- Physics S

Extracurricular Activities

Level Eleven Google CrowdSource Contributor

• February 2022 - Present

Member Rotaract Club of SLIIT

• December 2021 - Present

Director of Communications Mozilla Campus Club Of SLIIT

• November 2021 - Present

June 2019 — June 2023

Nov 2017 — April 2019

Aug 2014 — Aug 2018

Shashika Kahatanitiya

Blogger Medium • August 2021 - Present

• Data Analytics In Sports • Rise of Al Bot Technology

Member IEEE Society Of SLIIT

• June 2021 - Present • Publicity team member in event Launchpad

Work experience

DevArt Software Co.

July 2021 — Feb 2022

Remote C#.NET Software Engineer Internship

- This is a fully remote internship I have got in July. I worked on remote team-based web projects and individual projects.
- In here mainly I have done, creating and operating .NET based applications such as Windows Desktop Applications, Windows forms, and ASP.NET web applications Using layered and MVC Architecture.
- In addition to that, I have done an R & D project about Augmented reality for E-Commerce web applications and bug fixes of existing web applications.

APNLAB

Jan 2021 — April 2021

Remote C#. NET Trainee Web Developer

- This is a fully remote internship i have got in January. I worked on remote team-based web projects and individual projects.
- In here mainly I have done, creating and operating .NET based E-Commerce web applications such as Windows Desktop Applications, Windows forms, and ASP.NET web applications using MVC Architecture.
- In addition to that I have created Some .NET based Web APIs.

Skills

- C#
- Microsoft .NET Framework
- SQL, IIS, SQL SERVER
- Java/Bootstrap/JavaScript/CSS/HTML
- · Git, GitHub, Teams Explore
- ASP.NET, .NET Core, WEB APIs & Rest APIs
- · Laravel Framework Using PHP, MERN stack web development
- · Good Leadership Skills, Communication and presentation Skills, Decision making & Problem Solving Skills

Certificates and Licenses

- Postman Student Expert Postman 2022
- Learning ASP.NET Framework Course LinkedIn Learning 2021
- AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials AWS Educate 2021
- Coderally Hackerthon Competition 2021 IIT Campus
- Scrum Foundation Proffesional Certificate CertiProf 2021
- Road to CodeMania '21 IEEE Society in SLTC 2021
- Fundamentals of Digital Marketing Google digital Garage 2021
- Certified Microsoft Educator Microsoft Learning 2021
- Oracle Autonomous Database Explorer Batch Oracle University 2021
- Introduction to WebAPIs Linkedin Learning 2021
- Enterprise Architecture Foundations Linkedin Learning 2021
- Mern Stack Essential Training LinkedIn Learning 2021
- Github essential training course LinkedIn Learning 2021
- C# Course SoloLearn 2021

Shashika Kahatapitiya 2

- Node.js essential training course LinkedIn Learning 2021
- JavaScript Essential Training LinkedIn Learning 2021
- Crystal Reports Essential Training LinkedIn Learning 2021
- Web Accessibility Training By UNICEF 2021

Projects

- Employee Management Portal using .NET Core Web APIs , Vue.js , My SQL. 2022
- .NET Core three layered Architecture using Learning Management System 2022
- ASP.NET web application for Student Registration System 2021
- .NET Windows Desktop Application for Calculator 2021
- Augmented Reality based Research and Development E-Commerce Web Application Project using ASP.NET, AR.js, Html Canvas - 2021
- MERN web applications using REST API Build 2021
- "Rala" E-Commerce Web application using ASP.NET and Entity Framework 2021
- MVC ASP.NET Core Rest API Building With API Testing using Postman 2021
- "Store Master" Shopping Management System using Laravel framework based PHP 2021

References

- Pathum Bandara DEVART SOFTWARE CO. Pa@devart.lk
- Ms. Uthpala Samarakoon Department Coordinator Department of Information Technology SLIIT uthpala.s@sliit.lk

Shashika Kahatapitiya 3